George Miranda

Full Stack Web Developer

Address: Livermore, CA Phone: (209) 620-0032

Email: george92miranda@gmail.com

Github: github.com/FunkyGeorge Portfolio: aboutgeorge.net

Summary

I am not the average computer scientist that learned all his skills sitting in classrooms until he got a degree to get a tech job. I worked my way straight into a low level tech job and worked my way up through experience and curiosity. I believe I succeeded because people love to work with me and I am a great team player.

Why Me?

- **Collaborative** I love team work to ensure the best possible product.
- **Resourceful** Persistence helps me figure out problems using critical thinking.

Technical Skills

Languages: Javascript, C#, Swift, Python, Java, HTML/CSS

Tools: Node.js, Angular, React-Native, iOS, .NET, Flask, Bootstrap, jQuery, git

Databases: MySQL, MS SQL Server 2012, MongoDB **Software:** Visual Studio, Xcode, MySQL Workbench

Professional Experience

Full Stack Developer - Ronin Dev

October 2016 - Current

I currently work for an app agency. I am part of a four person team that works to get our clients a minimum viable product. This job consists of doing/knowing all parts of an app development cycle. This includes front end design, back end logic, database knowledge and deploying to servers.

Evergreen – This was our largest app that we created as a freelance development team. The idea is that makers and suppliers could have a platform to find and choose each other and get manufacturing contracts based on analytics. My role was factoring the entire front end into Angular and creating the formulas in the database to supply the users with valuable data that they could use to make purchasing decisions.

Visit the site at evergreenmake.com

Technologies - Angular, MySQL, Express.js, JavaScript, Node.js

IT Support-Quanta Computer

August 2015- August 2016

Assisted in keeping the flow of internal production as smooth as possible. I managed databases to make sure data was input and transferred correctly.

While I was here, I helped my IT team become more productive by automating a tedious label printing procedure. Although it was not my responsibility to create this, I took the initiative to create it with spare time so that the team could make better use of our time. This internal program soon was used by our production line which saved us even more time.

Associate Manager-Turlock Regal Cinema

April 2012-July 2015

2 years spent as an entry level floor staff before being promoted to Associate Manager. As a manager, you had to maintain the best possible customer satisfaction by making sure their experience was as enjoyable as possible. To do this required having a deep knowledge of the daily process.

Education

Onsite Web Development Bootcamp at Coding Dojo

Attended a web development course where 1000+ hours were put into learning the new technologies in today's world. The purpose of the course was to expose us to many modern web technologies so that we could learn to be flexible in the job market. This course included many group and individual projects that were built from the bottom up.

Modesto Junior College – Modesto, CA

Computer Science 60 credits